<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://zineglob.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://zineglob.com/collections/argan-achifae.atom"/>
  <title> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</title>
  <updated>2021-04-21T10:03:01+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/6556483944523</id>
    <published>2021-04-21T10:03:01+00:00</published>
    <updated>2021-04-21T10:03:01+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/amlou"/>
    <title>Amlou</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/AmlouofArgan.jpg?v=1618999382"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span data-mce-fragment="1">Amlou is a Berber exceptionally nourishing spread Food. It is ultra rich in protein and Vitamin E,  mineral salts and vitamins,digestive enzymes,</span><br data-mce-fragment="1"><span data-mce-fragment="1">Amlou is content of pure honey, sweet almond , and edible Argan oil. It is traditionally consumed in the Souss of Morocco ( Agadir ) in plat like breakfast and barcoucse. It helps with digestion and the absorption of fats, stimulates insulin release, contributes to lowering bad cholesterol levels, and provides energy and strength. It is thus particularly recommended in the morning every day.</span></p>
<p>Amlou an exceptionally Food Moroccan breakfast spread. Made with Sweet Almonds, Argan Oil, and USDA  organic and pure Honey. A must spread which complements Moroccan meal tray.</p>
<p>Moroccan Amlou is known all over the world. Who does not know the Bercoucs, Moroccan couscous, and the famous Moroccan Gastronomy.</p>
<p>Amlou always used a variety of bread. </p>
<p>Amlou is Somthing special for Berber Amazigh Women, Amlou is tradition of Our Life here in Souss Agadir from Child old, </p>
<p><span>Amlou is a Paste Berber Moroccan edible preparation made from sweet almonds, of organic argan oil and pure honey. It is a tonic that is served at breakfast, as a snack, in spreadable paste on barley bread, corn or wheat. Amlou Food also brings all kinds of pastry. The preparation is made on the basis of toasted almonds and looted, oil roasted Argan food and pure honey Natural.</span></p>
<p> </p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/6556483944523</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/6556482863179</id>
    <published>2021-04-21T09:50:50+00:00</published>
    <updated>2021-04-21T09:50:50+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/green-clay-mask"/>
    <title>Green Clay Skin Facial Mask</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/GreenClay.jpg?v=1618998651"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span data-mce-fragment="1">The Green Clay is found naturally in Morocco. It is composed of iron oxides and kelp seaweed, along with other decomposed plant matter, that contribute to its green color. The Green Clay Skin Facial Mask is mined from naturally occurring deposits, is then sun dried and crushed down to its finest form. Because of its unique healing properties, it has been widely used for centuries in both cosmetic and medicinal remedies.</span></p>
<p><span data-mce-fragment="1">Green Clay Skin Facial Mask is rich in magnesium, calcium, potassium, silicon, selenium, aluminum, titanium, cobalt, sodium, phosphorus, copper and zinc. This extraordinary blend of minerals makes French Green Clay one of the most absorbent cosmetic clays. With its negative charge and very fine texture, it acts as a magnet, drawing out the negatively charged toxins and poisons from the skin, washing away impurities and leaving your skin clear, smooth and hydrated. Compared to other clays, Green Clay Skin Facial Mask  not stripping like Bentonite Green Clay Mask and it is more absorbent than Kaolin Green Clay Skin Facial Mask , making it a better and safer choice for all skin types.</span></p>
<p><span>Green Clay Mask has a natural detoxifying properties, Green Clay Skin Facial Mask  is the best choice for naturally treating acne by going deep into the pores and removing impurities from our oil glands. It also regenerates healthy skin growth and decreases the reoccurrence of future breakouts.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<div id="gtx-anchor" style="position: absolute; visibility: hidden; left: 34px; top: 46px; width: 28px; height: 19px;"></div>
<div class="jfk-bubble gtx-bubble" role="alertdialog" aria-describedby="bubble-14" style="visibility: visible; left: 33px; top: 75px; opacity: 1;">
<div class="jfk-bubble-content-id" id="bubble-14">
<div id="gtx-host" style="min-width: 200px; max-width: 400px;"></div>
</div>
<div class="jfk-bubble-closebtn-id jfk-bubble-closebtn" aria-label="Close" role="button" tabindex="0"></div>
<div class="jfk-bubble-arrow-id jfk-bubble-arrow jfk-bubble-arrowup" style="left: 40px;">
<div class="jfk-bubble-arrowimplbefore"></div>
<div class="jfk-bubble-arrowimplafter"></div>
</div>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/6556482863179</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/6556481224779</id>
    <published>2021-04-21T09:41:20+00:00</published>
    <updated>2021-04-21T09:41:20+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/white-clay-facial-mask"/>
    <title>White Clay Skin Facial Mask</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/Whiteclay.jpg?v=1618998045"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span data-mce-fragment="1">The White Clay Also known as Kaolin Clay, White Clay is a very fine, soft and light powder with naturally absorbent properties. Gentle and smooth on skin, White Clay Skin Facial Mask is a great option for almost all skin types, working really well for normal skin types (skin that is neither oily nor dry), as well as mature skin. White Clay Skin Facial Mask works as a very mild exfoliant, gently removing dead and dry skin cells to leave you with clarified, glowing skin as well as reducing the size of your pores, which makes White Clay Skin Facial Mask the perfect pre-makeup masks, your foundation will just glide on! It also works to very gently draw out dirt, oil and grime from deep within the pores.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span>This </span> White Clay Skin Facial Mask<span> is a favourite of mine as it really works to gently cleanse and detoxify the skin, brightening the complexion and leaving your skin looking and feeling incredibly smooth. Harnessing the cleansing properties of Australian White Clay Skin Facial Mask, this purifying and brightening mask is ideal for all skin types, working to draw out impurities and absorb excess oil without stripping the skin of its natural moisture. Vegan, Australian made and Gluten Free, it can be mixed with water to form a paste, applied White Clay Skin Facial Mask to the face, then left on for 15 to 20 minutes.</span></p>
<div id="gtx-anchor" style="position: absolute; visibility: hidden; left: 38px; top: 207px; width: 141px; height: 19px;"></div>
<div class="jfk-bubble gtx-bubble" role="alertdialog" aria-describedby="bubble-7" style="visibility: visible; left: 94px; top: 91px; opacity: 1;">
<div class="jfk-bubble-content-id" id="bubble-7">
<div id="gtx-host" style="min-width: 200px; max-width: 400px;"></div>
</div>
<div class="jfk-bubble-closebtn-id jfk-bubble-closebtn" aria-label="Close" role="button" tabindex="0"></div>
<div class="jfk-bubble-arrow-id jfk-bubble-arrow jfk-bubble-arrowdown" style="left: 100.5px;">
<div class="jfk-bubble-arrowimplbefore"></div>
<div class="jfk-bubble-arrowimplafter"></div>
</div>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/6556481224779</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/6555791654987</id>
    <published>2021-04-19T10:45:15+00:00</published>
    <updated>2021-04-19T10:45:15+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/red-clay-skin-facial-mask"/>
    <title>Red Clay Skin Facial Mask</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/RedClay.jpg?v=1618828013"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><ul class="a-unordered-list a-vertical a-spacing-mini" data-mce-fragment="1">
<li data-mce-fragment="1"><span class="a-list-item" data-mce-fragment="1">PURE CLAY POWDER FOR FACIAL CLEANSING: Mediterranean red clay is a natural clay powder that is highly absorbent and mixes easily with water and other moisturizing products. It serves as an excellent facial cleanser and purifying mask, especially for individuals with sensitive skin.</span></li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1"><span class="a-list-item" data-mce-fragment="1">SENSITIVE SKIN TYPES: Use for sensitive skin in need of detoxification, pore cleansing, and improved skin tone. (Non-GMO Project Verified, Paraben Free, Vegan)</span></li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1"><span class="a-list-item" data-mce-fragment="1">NOW Solutions is the next step in the evolution of personal care products, formulated with the finest functional ingredients from around the world. NOW Solutions products avoid harsh chemical ingredients in our formulations, to provide a more natural product line. NOW Solutions products are not tested on animals. NOW Solutions products are analytically tested to assure the highest quality.</span></li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/6555791654987</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/6555792048203</id>
    <published>2021-04-19T10:42:23+00:00</published>
    <updated>2021-04-19T10:42:23+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/argan-oil-culinary"/>
    <title>Argan Oil Culinary Extra Virgin</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/ArganOilCulinary.jpg?v=1618828365"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p data-mce-fragment="1">It is our mission to offer the best quality  Extra Virgin Culinary Argan Oil as it is the best edible vegetable oil in the world. Deliciously tasting, superb in composition, and nutritious. The poster child for sustainable sourcing. Undiluted, pure and organic certified. Tested for centuries, rarely produced for use outside the local communities.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">Supply chain</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">* Based in morocco since 2006, we have established relations with the argan community involved in the Argan oil production and sharing our passion in providing the best product possible. Pure, undiluted- and tasty! We engage with scientists, researchers, share knowledge, participate in clinical trials studying the benefits of Argan oil for humans and publish results on this website.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">Sustainability</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">* Wild harvested by hand and respectfully sourced in the Argan Bio-Reservoir around Tardouant where the terroir is hilly. The argan trees root deep and sun and winds have positive effects on the quality of the argan fruits.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">* Cracked by hand, the kernels are selected for artisan roasting by our ‘maître torréfacteur’ monitoring temperature, time and texture.  After quality control, kernels are cold-pressed produced in small batches, with a rigid filtration process to provide top quality culinary argan oil.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">* Best in class manufacturing standards, with a keen eye on hygienic standards, are observed. Tests on the chemical composition -acidity-, texture, and taste ensure only the best quality, Extra Virgin, is released for bottling into our black colored bottles.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">Transparency</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Transparency in the value chain is key, and organic certification, such as 100% USDA organic, ensures standards are met and a paper trail on origin and pressing is documented. Before export, a government agency lab has to release shipments after testing on purity and acidity: Extra-Virgin or Virgin.            </p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">Delicious</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">But the taste is something different -and experience and knowledge matter to get a great tasting oil. Our Extra Virgin Argan Oil (EVAO) has a delightful nutty taste and is very versatile to cook, marinate, bake or finish with.  The result is a luminous oil balancing a slight flavor reminiscent of hazelnut and pistachio, with a crisp and pleasant robust finish. No worries about nut allergies, as the argan kernel is a stone fruit, just like a peach.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><strong data-mce-fragment="1">Healthy</strong></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Proven to help reduce cholesterol, cardiovascular disease and much more. Never diluted, nothing artificial added. Clean label: one ingredient. Tasty and Healthy, enjoy!</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/6555792048203</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1879223894074</id>
    <published>2018-09-05T15:33:34+01:00</published>
    <updated>2018-09-05T15:33:34+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/henna-moroccan-with-herbals-in-powder-200-gr"/>
    <title>HENNA MOROCCAN WITH HERBALS IN POWDER 200 Gr</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/Henna.jpg?v=1618571625"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>This is one of the most natural remedies used in oriental countries. Pure source of beauty and color, henna powder is usually used for body art and tattoos. As it’s applied to dye and cure hair and skin. It strengthens eyelashes and eyebrows, nourishes and softens the skin. This flowering plant grows in Morocco and its young leaves are dried out, milled and sifted to get green-brownish or light green powder. More than tanning agents of henna, this organic product provides precious gum and organic acids, vitamins C and K. It improves hair structure, by making it thicker and glossier. It eliminates the dandruff as it nourishes splitting and damaged locks and even cures hair loss.</span></p>
<p><span>Henna can be used as a natural hair dye, since it produces all shades of red. Mix the powder with hot water and some lemon juice to get light red, or with infused coffee to get a deep maroon shade. The used quantity depends on the lengh of hair. Colorless henna is ideal for a hair mask. Put 50g of colorless henna powder and add boiled water then leave the mixture for 5 to7 min. Apply the mask on the hair roots and on the whole length of your hair then wait for an hour. Wash and rinse you hair as usual. The colorless henna for skin is the perfect product to fight small wrinkles. Mix 10g of henna powder with a bit of boiled water and a couple of drops of lemon juice to create a face and body mask. Wait 5 minutes then rinse. With regular application once up to twice a week, the effect on the skin is simply superb!</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1879223894074</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1501744595002</id>
    <published>2018-06-19T15:33:58+01:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-19T15:33:58+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/morocco-beard-argan-oil"/>
    <title>Beard Oil of Moroccan Argan Oil 50ML AND 100ML</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/BeardOil.jpg?v=1618571112"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            27.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Our Morocco Beard Oil is an adventurous blend of exotic oils and spices — peppermint, cloves, vanilla, coffee, and precious resins. Upon applying the beard oil you immediately find yourself walking through a Moroccan market surrounded by exotic scents and sights — ready for whatever adventure might present itself.  For a true man of the world, Morocco will have you daydreaming endlessly of spontaneous adventures to faraway places.</p>
<p><b>Ingredients</b></p>
<p>Sweet Almond Oil, Safflower Oil, Grapeseed Oil, Jojoba Oil, Argan Oil, Fragrance*, Olive Oil, and Castor Oil</p>
<ul>
<li><span>Natural oils keep facial hair soft and reduce itchiness associated with beard growth</span></li>
<li><span>Exotic and inviting scent</span></li>
<li>Includes shaker insert to make dispensing easy</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1501744595002</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">27.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440902185018</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T10:30:53+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T10:30:53+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/bath-salts-with-essential-oils"/>
    <title>BATH SALTS WITH ESSENTIAL OILS 200GR</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor>arganorganic</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/BathSalt.jpg?v=1618571131"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>arganorganic<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>Beyond their great smell, the bath salts contain magnesium, potassium, calcium, bromide, and sodium. These minerals are easily absorbed by the pores to cleanse and purify the skin and to improve its radiance, tone, and texture. The presence of magnesium helps to fight fatigue and to release tension. Moreover calcium balances water retention while it helps stave off osteoporosis. Potassium keeps the skin moisturize when bromide soothes tired and sore muscles. Concerning sodium, it balances and manages the lymphatic fluid in our bodies. Over all the bath salts soothe and nourish the skin while it act efficiently on your mood. After your bath you will feel calm and relaxed.</span></p>
<div class="separator"><strong>How to use :</strong></div>
<p>Add a handful of bath salts into the hot water of your bathtub then relax in the bath for 15 to 20 minutes. Enjoy the multiple benefits of bath salts without any side effects.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440902185018</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440902185018</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440896254010</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T10:29:06+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T10:29:06+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/ghassoul-clay-in-powder-certified-organic"/>
    <title>GHASSOUL CLAY IN POWDER CERTIFIED ORGANIC 200GR</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor>arganorganic</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/GhassoulPowder.jpg?v=1618571424"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>arganorganic<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>Ghassoul or Lava Clay, is mined from ancient deposits within the Morocco Atlas Mountains. This clay is the result of natural geothermal processes and volcanic activity. Its very rich in minerals mainly silicon, magnesium, iron, sodium, potassium, lithium, and trace elements. That’s why it’s considered as an exceptional ingredient for skin and hair care. &lt;br&gt; Ghassoul has an incomparable ability to absorb impurities and excess of sebum. It lessens dryness, improves the skin clarity and elasticity and has extractive abilities that confiscate impurities and unblock pores.</span></p>
<div class="separator"><strong>How to use :</strong></div>
<p>It can be used as natural shampoo by mixing 50g of ghassoul with some water untill getting a paste to apply on the scalp and the hair. The same mixture can be used as face and body mask. It’s recommended to mix ghassoul with rose water to obtain better results.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Collection</s:tag>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440896254010</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440896254010</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440343195706</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T09:03:34+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T09:03:34+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/shampoo-of-rose"/>
    <title>SHAMPOO OF ROSE</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Rose Products</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/Roseshampoo.jpg?v=1618572013"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Rose Products<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>Adequate for both men and women, this shampoo is enriched with one of the most effective ingredients for hair and scalp health which is damascena rose. Its gentle foam cleans the scalp while nourishing it in depth with vitamins and antioxidents. It removes all dirtness and procures moisture, softness and volume.</span></p>
<div class="separator"><strong>How to use :</strong></div>
<p>Apply small quantity on the scalp, massage for few seconds to remove the dirtness and to stimulate blood circulation. Slide the foam all the way through the hair before rinsing thoroughly.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440343195706</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440343195706</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440334184506</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T08:57:49+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T08:57:49+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/conditioner-with-rose"/>
    <title>CONDITIONER WITH ROSE WATER 200ML</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Rose Products</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/Roseconditioner.jpg?v=1618571185"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Rose Products<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>This conditioner with rose water is indicated for dry and limp hair. Thanks to its formula rich in vitamins and antioxidents, it hydrates and moisturizes the hair deeply for a smooth and silky strands. It helps to deliver moisture where needed the most, it’s the product to include in everyday hair care routine. Use this conditioner after the shampoo with rose to deliver optimum benefits to your hair. It helps to repair dry and damaged hair, to catch up on regular hair washing routine, the conditioner with rose is the must product to enjoy hair that feels richly moisturized and more manageable, all in the time it takes to wash and rinse.</span></p>
<div class="separator"><strong>How to use :</strong></div>
<p>Wash your hair with rose shampoo, then rinse out and wring out your hair. Apply rose conditionner on hair’s strands and insist on the ends to nourish them deeply. Let the conditioner with rose set for 2 to 3 minutes then rinse out to get smoothy and silky hair.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p>
<div id="gtx-anchor" style="position: absolute; visibility: hidden; left: 145px; top: 10px; width: 78px; height: 17px;"></div>
<div class="jfk-bubble gtx-bubble" role="alertdialog" aria-describedby="bubble-2" style="visibility: visible; left: 169px; top: 37px; opacity: 1;">
<div class="jfk-bubble-content-id" id="bubble-2">
<div id="gtx-host" style="min-width: 200px; max-width: 400px;"></div>
</div>
<div class="jfk-bubble-closebtn-id jfk-bubble-closebtn" aria-label="Close" role="button" tabindex="0"></div>
<div class="jfk-bubble-arrow-id jfk-bubble-arrow jfk-bubble-arrowup" style="left: 176px;">
<div class="jfk-bubble-arrowimplbefore"></div>
<div class="jfk-bubble-arrowimplafter"></div>
</div>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440334184506</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440334184506</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440305250362</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T08:55:41+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T08:55:41+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/rose-hard-soap"/>
    <title>ROSE HARD SOAP 75GR</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Rose Products</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/RoseSoap.jpg?v=1618571926"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Rose Products<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>It is made in respect of the nature and the comoposition of damascena rose. The roses used in this soap are not denatured to be profitable the most to the user. This rose hard soap is rich in natural glycerin and it doesn’t contain any animal fats. Rose hard soap is gentle cleanser to be introduced in daily hygiene routine, since it is not aggressive for the film hydrolipidic skin. This true care washing has soothing and conditioning effects since it’s made with damascena roses which balance skin’s PH.</span></p>
<div class="separator">
<span>How to use</span><span> :</span>
</div>
<p>This rose hard soap is the perfect cleanser for both face and body. To use twice a day for perfect hygiene and it can replace easily the shower gel.</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440305250362</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440305250362</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440293748794</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T08:54:29+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T08:54:29+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/milk-body-lotion-of-rose"/>
    <title>MILK BODY LOTION OF ROSE 200ML</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Rose Products</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/RoseMilk.jpg?v=1618571683"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Rose Products<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>Nourishing lotion with damascena rose, this milk body lotion rapidly hydrates, nourishes and protects the skin. It’s rich with essential nutrients and vitamins for skin’s daily requirements to provide maximum vitality and softness. This milk body lotion with damascena rose is suitable for all skin types.</span></p>
<div class="separator"><strong>How to use :</strong></div>
<p>Apply small quantity on the skin and massage gently to help the penetration of the components deeply in the epidermis. The smell is amazing to perfume your body while moisturizing and nurishing it. Do not rinse after use.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440293748794</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440293748794</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440281198650</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T08:52:04+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T08:52:04+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/cream-of-rose"/>
    <title>CREAM OF ROSE 200GR</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Rose Products</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/RoseCream.jpg?v=1618571359"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Rose Products<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>This cream is enriched with natural rose which provides vitamins and antioxidants. This moisturizer hydrates and refreshes the skin. It prevents the apparition of wrickles, fine lines, dark spots and the epidermis loosening too. It nourishes deeply the skin and provides maximum vitality and softness.</span></p>
<div class="separator"><strong>How to use :</strong></div>
<p>Wash your face with rose hard soap, then apply this cream twice a day on clean skin, massage for a minute to help the penetration of the nutrients.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440281198650</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440281198650</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440270876730</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T08:50:38+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T08:50:38+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/rose-dry-flower"/>
    <title>ROSE FLOWER DRY  200GR</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Rose Products</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/RoseFlower.jpg?v=1618571909"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Rose Products<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>Damascena roses are a main ingredient in many medical remedies and even cosmetics. This natural product is just perfect to fight depression, to kill germs and bacteria, to solve the problem of lack of appetite and anorexia, to heal liver congestion, nausea, kidney stones and bladder infections among other problems. Damascena roses are efficient againt insomnia, anxiety and apathy as they help to prevent  depression. They are also related to female beauty and used in skincare regimes. This product is used as face toner, tightening on capillaries and redness reducer. Damascena roses are amazing for their  cleansing and antiseptic caracteristics, they prevent rashes, swelling, sores and cuts.</span></p>
<div class="separator">
<span>How to use</span><span> :</span>
</div>
<p>Damascena roses can be ground to use the powder as a hair or facial mask. As it can be added to ghassoul or henna. Just add a handful of roses in the bathtub to enjoy a flavored steam bath as well as the benefits of damascina petals that regulate the PH of the skin.</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440270876730</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440270876730</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440246104122</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T08:45:50+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T08:45:50+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/prickly-pear-seeds-oil-hard-soap"/>
    <title>PRICKLY PEAR SEEDS OIL HARD SOAP 75GR</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/PricklyPearSoap.jpg?v=1618571861"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>It is made in respect of cosmetic oil of prickly pear. The oil used in this soap is not heated or denatured to be profitable the most to the user. This prickly pear hard soap is rich in natural glycerin and it doesn’t contain any animal fats known as sodium tallowate. Prickly pear hard soap is gentle cleanser to be introduced in daily hygiene routine, since it is not aggressive for the film hydrolipidic skin. This true care washing has soothing and conditioning effects since it’s made with prickly pear oil which is rich in vitamin K and fatty acids.</span></p>
<div class="separator">
<span>How to use</span><span> :</span>
</div>
<p>This prickly pear hard soap is the perfect cleanser for both face and body. To use twice a day for perfect hygiene and it can replace easily the shower gel.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440246104122</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440246104122</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440239386682</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T08:44:39+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T08:44:39+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/conditioner-of-prickly-pear-seeds-oil"/>
    <title>CONDITIONER OF PRICKLY PEAR SEEDS OIL 200ML</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/Pricklypearconditioner.jpg?v=1618571050"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>This conditioner with prickly pear oil is indicated for dry and limp hair. Thanks to its formula rich in vitamin K and fatty acids, it hydrates and moisturizes the hair deeply for a smooth and silky strands. It helps to deliver moisture where needed the most, it’s the product to include in every day hair care routine. Use this conditioner after the shampoo with prickly pear oil to deliver optimum benefits to your hair. It helps to repair dry and damaged hair, to catch up on regular hair washing routine, the conditioner with prickly pear oil is the must product to enjoy hair that feels richly moisturized and more manageable, all in the time it takes to wash and rinse.</span></p>
<div class="separator"><strong>How to use : </strong></div>
<p>Wash your hair with prickly pear oil shampoo, then rinse out and wring out your hair. Apply conditionner on hair’s strands and insist on the ends to nourish them deeply. Let the conditioner with prickly pear oil set for 2 to 3 minutes then rinse out to get smoothy and silky hair.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440239386682</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440239386682</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440231653434</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T08:43:14+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T08:43:14+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/shampoo-of-prickly-pear-oil"/>
    <title>SHAMPOO OF PRICKLY PEAR OIL</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor>arganorganic</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/Pricklypearshampoo.jpg?v=1618571997"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>arganorganic<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>Adequate for both men and women, this shampoo is enriched with one of the most effective oils for hair and scalp health which is prickly pear seeds oil. Its gentle foam cleans the scalp while nourishing it in depth with vitamin K and fatty acids. It removes all darkness and procures moisture, softness and volume.</span></p>
<div class="separator"><strong>How to use :</strong></div>
<p>Apply a small quantity on the scalp, massage for seconds to remove the dirtness and to stimulate blood circulation. Slide the foam all the way through the hair before rinsing thoroughly.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440231653434</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440231653434</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440221036602</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T08:41:53+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T08:41:53+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/milk-body-lotion-of-prickly-pear-seeds-oil"/>
    <title>MILK BODY LOTION OF PRICKLY PEAR SEEDS OIL 200 ML</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/PricklypearMilk.jpg?v=1618571657"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>Nourishing blends with organic prickly pear oil, this milk body lotion rapidly hydrates, nourishes and protects the skin. It’s rich with essential nutrients and vitamins for skin’s daily requirements to provide maximum vitality and softness. This milk body lotion with prickly pear oil is suitable for all skin types.</span></p>
<div class="separator"><strong>How to use :</strong></div>
<p>Apply small quantity on the skin and massage gently to help the penetration of the components deeply in the epidermis. The smell is amazing to perfume your body while moisturising and nurishing it. Do not rinse after use.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440221036602</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440221036602</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440209240122</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T08:39:44+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T08:39:44+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/prickly-pear-seeds-oil"/>
    <title>PRICKLY PEAR SEEDS OIL 30ML</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/PricklyPearOil.jpg?v=1618571838"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            29.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><blockquote>
<p><span>Prickly pear seeds oil is 100% pure and organic product, obtained by first cold pressing to preserve its organoleptic qualities. It’s certified organic product which doesn’t contain any added flavors, dyes or preservatives. It’s rich in vitamin K and fatty acids which are main sources for beautiful skin and hair.</span></p>
<p><span> It’s a powerful antioxidant that slows cells aging, stimulates their renewal, reduces the number and depth of wrinkles and fine lines under the eyes and calms sunburn. It’s very efficient to heal scars and it makes the skin firm smooth and improves its elasticity. It tightens pores, nourishes and moisturizes the skin and the hair in depth for a perfect result.</span></p>
<p class="separator"><strong>How to use :</strong></p>
<p>To apply on clean skin or hair and to massage for few minutes, to help the penetration of the components. This oil is not greasy and doesn’t leave any oily or sticky film. Use it by daily basis to help your hair and skin regain radiance, shine, and softness.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p>
</blockquote></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Collection</s:tag>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440209240122</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440209240122</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">29.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440186564666</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T08:38:04+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T08:38:04+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/argan-oil-hard-soap"/>
    <title>ARGAN OIL HARD SOAP 75GR</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/ArganSoap.jpg?v=1618571145"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>It is made in respect of cosmetic oil of argan. The organic argan oil used in this soap is not heated or denatured to be profitable the most to the user. This argan hard soap is rich in natural glycerin and it doesn’t contain any animal fats (sodium tallowate). Argan hard soap is a gentle cleanser to be introduced in daily hygiene routine, since it is not aggressive for the film hydrolipidic skin. This true care washing has soothing and conditioning effects since it’s made with argan oil which is rich in vitamin E and fatty acids.</span></p>
<div class="separator"><strong>How to use :</strong></div>
<p>This argan hard soap is the perfect product for cleaning the face and the whole body. To use twice a day for perfect hygiene and it can replace easily the shower gel.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440186564666</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440186564666</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440153370682</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T08:31:59+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T08:31:59+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/conditioner-of-argan-oil"/>
    <title>CONDITIONER OF ARGAN OIL 200ML</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/ArganConditioner.jpg?v=1618571077"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><div class="col-md-7">
<div class="product-summary">
<div class="short-description">
<p>This conditioner with argan oil is indicated for dry and limp hair. Thanks to its formula rich in vitamin E and fatty acids, it hydrates and moisturizes the hair deeply for a smooth and silky strands. It helps to deliver moisture where needed the most, it’s the product to include in everyday hair care routine. Use this conditioner after the shampoo with argan oil to deliver optimum benefits to your hair. It helps to repair dry and damaged hair, to catch up on regular hair washing routine, the conditioner with argan oil is the must product to enjoy hair that feels richly moisturized and more manageable, all in the time it takes to wash and rinse.</p>
</div>
<div class="cart-form-wrapper mt-30">
<form enctype="multipart/form-data" method="post" class="cart" action="https://zineglob.com/cart.php"><strong>How to use :</strong></form>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="col-md-12">
<div class="horizontal-tab product-tab">
<div class="tab-content">
<div class="tab-pane fade in active" id="tab1">
<p>Wash your hair with argan oil shampoo, then rinse out and wring out your hair. Apply conditionner on hair’s strands and insist on the ends to nourish them deeply. Let the conditioner with argan oil set for 2 to 3 minutes then rinse out to get smoothy and silky hair.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440153370682</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440153370682</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440145014842</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T08:30:39+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T08:30:39+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/shampoo-of-argan-oil"/>
    <title>SHAMPOO OF ARGAN OIL</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/ArganShampoo.jpg?v=1618571977"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong> ZINEGLOB | First producer of Organic Moroccan Argan oil<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><div class="col-md-7">
<div class="product-summary">
<div class="short-description">
<p>Adequate for both men and women, this shampoo is enriched with one of the most effective oils for hair and scalp health which is argan oil. Its gentle foam cleans the scalp while nourishing it in depth with vitamin E and fatty acids. It removes all dirtness and procures moisture, softness and volume.</p>
</div>
<div class="cart-form-wrapper mt-30">
<form enctype="multipart/form-data" method="post" class="cart" action="https://zineglob.com/cart.php"></form>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="col-md-12">
<div class="horizontal-tab product-tab">
<div class="tab-content">
<div class="tab-pane fade in active" id="tab1">
<div class="separator"><strong>How to use :</strong></div>
<p>Apply small quantity on the scalp, massage for few secondes to remove the dirtness and to stimulate blood circulation. Slide the foam all the way through the hair before rinsing thoroughly.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440145014842</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440145014842</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440138133562</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T08:28:26+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T08:28:26+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/argan-and-prickly-pear-dry-mask-for-hair"/>
    <title>ARGAN AND PRICKLY PEAR DRY MASK FOR HAIR 200GR</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Argan Oil Products , Prickly Pear Oil Products</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/ArganPricklypearpowder.jpg?v=1618570979"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Argan Oil Products , Prickly Pear Oil Products<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><div class="col-md-7">
<div class="product-summary">
<p>This is a natural mixture of argan and prickly pear powders, which can be used as shampoo or as mask to detox and purify the scalp and the skin. This combination is adequate for all hair and skin types. Mixed with rose water it can be applied on hair for more volume or on the scalp and skin to remove all dirtness and to get smoothness, health and firmness. This powder is a traditional shampoo and skin mask, use it to resorb the excess of sebum and to balance the PH of scalp and skin.</p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="col-md-12">
<div class="horizontal-tab product-tab">
<div class="tab-content">
<div class="tab-pane fade in active" id="tab1">
<div class="separator"><strong>How to use :</strong></div>
<p>It can be used as conditioner during shower or as mask to apply on clean skin for 10 to 15 minutes.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440138133562</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440138133562</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440108740666</id>
    <published>2018-06-11T08:24:06+00:00</published>
    <updated>2018-06-11T08:24:06+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://zineglob.com/products/milk-body-lotion-with-argan-oil"/>
    <title>MILK BODY LOTION WITH ARGAN OIL 200ML</title>
    <s:type>argane achifae</s:type>
    <s:vendor>arganorganic</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0105/6951/5066/products/ArganMilk.jpg?v=1618571783"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>arganorganic<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>argane achifae<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            0.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><div class="col-md-7">
<div class="product-summary">
<div class="short-description">
<p>Nourishing blends with organic argan oil, this milk body lotion rapidly hydrates, nourishes and protects the skin. It’s rich with essential nutrients and vitamins for skin’s daily requirements to provide maximum vitality and softness. This milk body lotion is suitable for all skin types.</p>
</div>
<div class="cart-form-wrapper mt-30">
<form enctype="multipart/form-data" method="post" class="cart" action="https://zineglob.com/cart.php"></form>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="col-md-12">
<div class="horizontal-tab product-tab">
<div class="tab-content">
<div class="tab-pane fade in active" id="tab1">
<div class="separator"><strong>How to use :<span mce-data-marked="1"></span></strong></div>
<p>Apply small quantity on the skin and massage gently to help the penetration of the components deeply in the epidermis. The smell is amazing to perfume your body while moisturising and nurishing it. Do not rinse after use.</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1LlCXgwsDD4?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>no-timer</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Private label</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440108740666</id>
      <title>Our Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://zineglob.com/products/1440108740666</id>
      <title>Your Private Label</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">0.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
